{
    "id": "9d8d0df9e9b44d7db365802e9f9a7df3",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I am confident …………………….. you will win.",
            "description": "We use that to introduce a noun clause. ",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "of",
                "whether"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. she read the letter, she started crying.",
            "description": "As soon as is used to say that something will happen immediately after something else has happened. ",
            "answers": [
                "As soon as",
                "Even as",
                "As long as"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He took the tablet ……………………… the pain would alleviate.",
            "description": "So that is used to express the purpose. ",
            "answers": [
                "so that",
                "so as to",
                "in order to"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. he is not interested, we will have to find someone else.",
            "description": "If expresses a condition. ",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I visited a restaurant …………………….. they sell exotic seafood.",
            "description": "We can use where to introduce adverb clauses of place.",
            "answers": [
                "there",
                "where",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The soldiers fought bravely ……………………… the enemy was stronger than them.",
            "description": "We use but to connect two independent clauses expressing contrasting ideas.",
            "answers": [
                "but",
                "though",
                "however"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He bit more ………………………. he could chew.",
            "description": "We use than after a comparative expression.",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "then"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. I don’t get this job, I will be in trouble.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… I get my raise, I will quit my job.",
            "description": "Unless means the same as if not.",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The laptop ……………………….. I bought yesterday is very expensive.",
            "description": "Both which and that can refer to objects in identifying relative clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Work hard …………………………… you will succeed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "so",
                "because"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He quit ………………………. he was dejected.",
            "description": "Because gives the reason. ",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "so",
                "hence"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}